The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
It's imperative we restore the public's faith in the magic knights
so that everyone feels safe and secure again,
while also improving the morale among the squads.
If we can do that, then we'll be much better prepared
to face spade and triumph over the devil.
Sorry, what exactly are you suggesting, sir?
I'm going to have the captains battle each other.
Folks, the magic knight smart captains are going head to head
in a team battle, and it begins now!
I would've fought in one way.
I'm planning another part.
But Iилиi in a domain.
Excuse me for the째OOOO sfly.
All right, mate.
Start the fight!
七色の日常を進め
永遠に光れ
Shine like a demon
天使と悪魔が交際してく
世界は矛盾だらけさ
思い通りじゃない
そのくらいで
負ける夢はダサい
そう
何度も何度も
目の前の壁を越えるさ
良さの未来に繋げよう
七色の日常を進め
永遠に光れ
Shine like a diamond
恋 pau
天使と悪魔が交際しており
翌日に祝った
フレットしてく
The fight will last for half an hour.
During that time, whichever team manages to destroy
the other team's crystal while protecting their own
will be recognized as the winners!
Also, the match will be broadcast kingdom-wide
so that everyone may witness it!
This is your chance to marvel at the amazing skills
of these great mages whom I personally spilled
blood, sweat, and tears to train soon!
You're welcome!
By the way, due to unforeseen circumstances,
Captain Real Boy-Boy-Tier of the Aqua Deer
will not be participating today!
Oh Master Real, those melancholy sighs are a sign
that you've fallen in love, your first step into adulthood.
Miss, I wish I could figure out who you are
or in where I'm supposed to find you.
Thanks for your help, Marks.
With your communication magic,
everyone in the kingdom can enjoy this historic event.
I'm happy to hear that, sir.
How much longer do I have to wear this disguise?
Poor Julius! Take it easy!
With the Wizard King out of commission,
I've got a golden chance to gain favor with the populace!
Now that I think about it,
we really should come up with a different solution to that,
for Owen's sake.
World Tree Magic!
Magic Tree Descent!
I won't let you interfere!
You're leading with that?
Summering magic!
Yes, I!
Not too shabby, Stringbean.
Dark magic.
Dark cloak.
I'll slice you up.
Of course.
I knew this would be complicated.
Count the distance so I can't catch it.
As did I.
Well then.
Let's keep to the plan.
Understood.
Just a粉회 in time,
Bulls. And now I have to fight the army. No, don't think about that. Remain calm. Calm.
Let's do our best. I'm psyched. You?
I am. Let's fight.
I don't remember the last time I had this many targets to cut up. You're all mine.
This guy is like a kid in a candy shop.
Not so fast. Of course the riffraff barrels right in.
That's all right. We'll focus on defending our crystal.
Care, care! Come out, come out wherever you are!
Do you even know where you're going, smart guy?
I don't recall asking your opinion, pal.
Just saying. Walking around in the open like this is a pretty good way to get ambushed.
Care. Like I care about playing it safe.
If you don't want to get cut up, you've just got to cut them first.
Mercury magic.
Brain of silver!
You should know your meager spells are nowhere near sufficient to stop an opponent such as myself.
And you should be well aware that whenever I run away, it's always a tactical retreat.
Very well.
Then whatever plan you may have, it'll burn to ash along with you.
Sir Nozell, please allow me to assist you.
When I fought Sir Fuegolion, I was no match for his power.
Despite having my vortex magic amplified by elven mana,
this is a chance for me to redeem myself.
I have a plan. Just follow my lead.
I'm getting used to being the king's right-hand man.
The citizens must be clamoring to learn more about me.
I bet they're like,
Who's that hottie standing next to his majesty?
Ha-ha!
It's me.
Sekei, I hope you know that if any of the captains hurl their attacks in my direction,
you'll be expected to protect me with your very life.
Huh?
Nope.
You're on your own, buddy.
Oh yeah, real clever of you,
picking away at your opponents little by little,
always maintaining a safe distance.
Now come closer!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Dark magic, black hole!
Interesting.
Dark magic, dark blood, lifeless man!
Dark magic, dark magic, dark magic, dark magic!
Mercury creation magic!
Silver star of execution!
Oh, I'm sorry.
We totally just hold that force, didn't we?
Now you've got nowhere left to hide.
Quite all right.
That stunt put a sizable dent in your magic reserves.
Dark magic, dark magic, dark magic, dark magic, dark magic.
Dark magic, dark magic, dark magic, dark magic, dark magic, dark magic, dark magic.
Please work now.
How beautiful!
It would appear our brilliant Captain Dorothy has lured Yami of the Black Bulls into her
lovely world of dreams, but unfortunately, communication magic isn't capable of crossing
over into that realm, which means the rest of us won't be able to bask in the splendor
of their magnificent battle until she brings them back.
There's something so beautiful about a fight that can't be observed.
I used my dream magic to transport you to Glamour World.
Might as well relax until time runs out, Yami dear.
You bet.
My squad tells me if you fall asleep in here, then you won't be able to go outside ever
again.
Oh, and whatever random crap you imagine becomes real, right?
Exactly.
Well then, onsen, sushi boat, and good sake!
It has to be something that I'm familiar with or it won't work!
Oh man, I was really looking forward to that.
Oh well.
Exit door.
That little elf who was possessing my body before had a hard time with specificity.
But I'm not going to make the same mistake.
I guess I'll have to take a direct approach.
It's more my style anyway.
Sounds like a plan.
Okay.
How do you like this?
Now, dark cloaked.
Lightless black!
Howdy, partner.
It's nice to meet you.
My name's Yami, and I'm the rootin' chitin' captain of the famous Black Bull Squad!
Is she making fun of me, or does she really think I talk like that?
The foreigner's mana disappeared.
He must have been captured by the dream magic.
He won't be escaping for a while.
We need to protect ourselves from any further setbacks.
Let's take care of him now.
Leave it to me.
Normally, I would have the upper hand against mercury magic.
But since he's constantly using a massive amount of mana, he can repair the cage instantly.
And I can't touch them if they're outside the vortex.
Quite clever.
He's trapped!
Wide-range mercury magic and a vortex.
With sophisticated techniques like that, they're formidable opponents even for Captain Flaygoleon.
Amazing.
So this is how captains fight.
Just wait.
My brother's still getting warmed up.
What do you think he's about to do with all those flames?
The fire won't reach us, but the heat will.
What's he plotting?
How hot is the blast going to be?
What?
Which way did he go?
He used salamander as a decoy so we wouldn't detect his mana.
Nice try!
I'm toast.
You should have known a copycat could never outdo the original.
I hate to tell you, but you're still within reach of her spell.
Cool thing about copies is, I can just keep creating more.
Huh.
Send all the knockoffs you want to.
Crap.
This sucks.
Now, Dark Clothes!
Dark Clothes!
Lightless Slash!
How did you...?
The signal is a bit faint but I'm picking up on Jack's mana.
Things look grim.
However, if we can hit him with one attack, we may still have a chance of winning this!
Dark Clothes!
I'm surprised you haven't given up yet.
Mercury magic!
Silver shining regal spear!
No! I can't hold out for much longer!
You've seemed so confident before, Jack.
Don't tell me this is the best you can do!
Nice work, Yami-deer!
You're tougher than I thought.
Although, I'm sure you're close to your limit.
Think so, eh?
Guess you've got a lot to learn about me then, little Miss Witch.
I'll show you the spell I used a while back.
A time when I really pushed past my limits!
Can you move?
Who do you think you're talking to, royal boy?
Let's have this fight, now!
I don't take orders from snubs like you!
Hold nothing back!
I don't think so.
As a royal who guards this kingdom, and as captain of the Silver Eagles, I refuse to be defeated in such a pathetic manner!
I'm sure you're watching, Crimson Lion Kings! Remember, there is nothing our passionate flames cannot incinerate!
Since I'm a squad captain, I have to be extra strong!
I want to become so good at dream magic, that I can even trap Devils in here!
You guys are all copies of the version of me that the little witch girl saw!
The thing is, I've gotten better since then!
Mono-Zo-Dark-Cloat-Dimension-slash-Equimont!
Oh my! Talk about a fantastic battle!
I can't believe I got to witness such an astounding exchange of magic power!
Especially the grand finale!
Who could have expected that Yami's Dimension-slash would cut both teams' crystals into at the same time!
You made us go through all that trouble and it's a tie?
Well, if somebody hadn't spent the whole battle in La La Land...
I think we can all agree those two are hopeless.
After such an exhausting competition, it's impressive they still have enough energy to argue.
What a bummer!
I was hoping I would get to be on the broadcast, but Yami-deer had to go and spend the whole fight stuck in the glamour world!
Yami-deer? What happened between those two?
I'm still in shock! You magic knight captains always find a new way to surprise me!
Something tells me he just wanted to watch the greats in action.
You were amazing too, Marx!
Thanks to you, the entire Clover Kingdom was lucky enough to be part of this unforgettable event!
Not only that, but I bet it made them feel much safer knowing that a group of capable mages like you are protecting them.
And after seeing all of you captains, rather grand magic knights in action, your subordinates will have an even higher opinion of you from this day forward.
Every moment brings us closer to facing Spade and the Devil.
I hope today's contest inspired you and your squads to reach even greater heights until then.
Sir!
I'mOTT!
I personally hurt.
If you Państwo are hitting someone,
I can still be faced with 홍 art.
This whole world is getting hardance,
I won't you?
今目の前に残るのは希望か
掴みかけたわずかな幸福が
まだ消せない誓い叫んでる 忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くだって 全然届かなくても
信じる君は足掻いて前を向いている
だから枯れないようにやらがって
描いた夢また歩き出せる
きっと僕を呼ぶ声だ
月て運んでいる
より苦しそう
ワークラス
Earthy's dream world was giving you quite a bit of trouble.
What exactly was going on in there?
Oh, it was a huge pain.
This other version of me showed up, and he was pretty freaking strong.
It sucked.
Another version of Yami?
You got the sexy Yami?
Or me, the wild Yami?
Which do you prefer?
The days pass, and time continues to flow.
Even I cannot turn back the clock.
Tomorrow will always come.
Black Clover, page 152, to Tomorrow.
I'm glad to know our kingdom's future is in good hands.